JESSICA CRUMP

Newly certified full-stack web developer from UCLA's coding bootcamp leveraging a diverse background of psychology, chemistry, biology, teaching, and language acquisition to use data and research to build an intuitive, elegant, and comfortable user experience. 1112 S UNIVERSITY BLVD. DENVER, CO 80210

(601) 668-9467

<u>Jessicacrump7@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u>

EXPERIENCE

PEACE CORPS — TEFL TEACHER

JANUARY 2020 - MARCH 2020, QUITO, ECUADOR

Committed 2 years to teaching English as a second language to Ecuadorian high school students | Evacuated early due to COVID-19

OXFORD CANTEEN — MANAGER

AUGUST 2017 - AUGUST 2019, OXFORD, MS

Trained numerous employees, delegated work, counted and balanced cash registers

UNIVERSITY OF MISSISSIPPI — SI LEADER

AUGUST 2018 – MAY 2019, OXFORD, MS

Taught Spanish to university students | Planned and lead 3 sessions weekly

EDUCATION

UCLA CODING BOOTCAMP — WEB DEVELOPMENT

OCTOBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021, REMOTE

Learned full-stack web development | Finished with an Ain course

UNIVERSITY OF MISSISSIPPI — B.A. PSYCHOLOGY

AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2019, OXFORD, MS

Minors in Spanish, chemistry, biology | Final mGPA: 3.87

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO

https://immense-lake-19917.herokuapp.com/

SKILLS

Problem solving

Teachable

Quick learner

Work well under pressure

LANGUAGES & TOOLS

Spanish | Conversational

 HTML

CSS

Javascript

React.js

Node.js

MongoDB | Mongoose ODM

MySQL | Sequelize

Express

LEADERSHIP & OTHER

Developmental Cognitive

Psychology Lab, U of M - Research

Assistant for 1.5 years

Held 1 presidency, 2 Vice presidencies, and 2 chairs 2018-19

Held 5 chairs 2017-18